<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Philosophical Connections - Group 1</title><link>https://c-wejendorp.github.io/finalProject_group1/</link><description>Recent content on Philosophical Connections - Group 1</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://c-wejendorp.github.io/finalProject_group1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Data collection</title><link>https://c-wejendorp.github.io/finalProject_group1/data-description/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://c-wejendorp.github.io/finalProject_group1/data-description/</guid><description>Wikipedia offers a list of philosophers divided into subfields, e.g., logician and ethicist, of which common web scraping techniques using Python’s request module was used to collect information on all listed philosophers. Additional information was added using Wikipedia’s sister project Wikidata, where the corresponding page is found using what is called a Q-code. The following attributes were collected:
href - The link to the wiki page q_code - The Q-code of the wiki page label - The label of the wikidata page subfields - A list of subfields the philosopher was found in links_to - All philosophers found in hyperlinks located in each page year - The known year of birth sex - Sex of philosopher country - Known country of citizenship info - The year of birth, sex, and country of citizenship When collecting href nuisance pages were filtered away.</description></item><item><title>Network 1</title><link>https://c-wejendorp.github.io/finalProject_group1/network-analysis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://c-wejendorp.github.io/finalProject_group1/network-analysis/</guid><description>Top 10 philosophers In-degree Out-degree Aristotle 163 Friedrich Nietzsche 61 Immanuel Kant 161 Martin Heidegger 54 Plato 135 Jacques Derrida 52 Bertrand Russell 109 Boethius 51 Karl Marx 102 Georg Wilhelm Friedrich Hegel 51 John Stuart Mill 94 Charles Fourier 50 Ludwig Wittgenstein 82 Claude Henri de Rouvroy 49 David Hume 78 Eduard Bernstein 49 John Locke 77 Michel Foucault 49 Albert Einstein 64 Slavoj Žižek 49 td { text-align: center; } .</description></item><item><title>Network 2</title><link>https://c-wejendorp.github.io/finalProject_group1/text-analysis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://c-wejendorp.github.io/finalProject_group1/text-analysis/</guid><description>text here
worclouds</description></item></channel></rss>