<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Philosophical Connections - Group 1</title><link>https://c-wejendorp.github.io/finalProject_group1/</link><description>Recent content on Philosophical Connections - Group 1</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://c-wejendorp.github.io/finalProject_group1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Data collection</title><link>https://c-wejendorp.github.io/finalProject_group1/data-description/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://c-wejendorp.github.io/finalProject_group1/data-description/</guid><description>Wikipedia offers a list of philosophers divided into subfields, e.g., logician and ethicist, of which common web scraping techniques using Python’s request module was used to collect information on all listed philosophers. Additional information was added using Wikipedia’s sister project Wikidata, where the corresponding page is found using what is called a Q-code. The following attributes were collected:
href - The link to the wiki page q_code - The Q-code of the wiki page label - The label of the wikidata page subfields - A list of subfields the philosopher was found in links_to - All philosophers found in hyperlinks located in each page year - The known year of birth sex - Sex of philosopher country - Known country of citizenship info - The year of birth, sex, and country of citizenship When collecting href nuisance pages were filtered away.</description></item><item><title>Network 1</title><link>https://c-wejendorp.github.io/finalProject_group1/network-analysis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://c-wejendorp.github.io/finalProject_group1/network-analysis/</guid><description>On this page the graph is constructed and analyzed. Using the links_to attribute, a directional graph is created. This results in a graph containing 1.809 nodes and 11.151 edges. This reduction from 2111 philosophers is due to removal of isolated nodes, i.e., philosophers that neither refer to others or are referred to. Because of the directional nature, edges will be both ingoing and outgoing with respect to the nodes. First a scatter plot is shown, where each point represents the count of out-degree vs in-degree.</description></item><item><title>Network 2</title><link>https://c-wejendorp.github.io/finalProject_group1/text-analysis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://c-wejendorp.github.io/finalProject_group1/text-analysis/</guid><description>text here
worclouds</description></item></channel></rss>